[{"answer": "They might be, Piers.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Are they potentially connecting the two?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Piers, we really don't.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Do we know how radicalized she may have been herself throughout the last two, three years?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Do you go with Eric Holder on this or do you think there is cause for concern?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Yes, so I think those are both very significant and the problem is right now we're dependent on Russian intelligence authorities for these stories right now.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "What do you read into these two connections that may have been established?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Well, I think it could help people to have an ease with being able to have a resting place for their loved one.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "How important do you think it will be to them that something is found eventually?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I'm doing well.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Ben, how are you?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "It depends on if you're pledging allegiance to a terrorist organization and you're working with foreign terrorists and around the world.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Isn't he entitled to the very constitutional rights that you hold so dear?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "But this is what we've seen.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Why would you find that so hard to believe when you've had home-grown terrorists who have done exactly that, who have exactly done what you just described?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "This is not the fourth of July where I throw a bottle rocket at you and you throw one back and we're playing.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Why was that logic of your argument on guns not applying here?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, of course, there's always the right of the people to amend the constitution.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Is there an argument that there should be?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Well, there are a lot of issues there that are going to be very, very controversial.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "How will it play out, do you think?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Their argument is that we're like a Visa or MasterCard.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "That means you're not his employer?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Well, I think for me, I left my country so I could be who I was in '75, and I didn't come out until '81 because I really couldn't be public about my sexuality because that would have disqualified me from, perhaps, being a U.S. citizen.", "docId": "130429pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "And will he be feeling that, too, do you think?", "qSentId": 472}]